<resources>

    <string name="app_name">CleanMoney</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="drawer_header">Home</string>
    <string name="drawer_mis">MIS</string>
    <string name="drawer_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="drawer_status">Status</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="previous_response">Previous Response:</string>
    <string name="current_response">Current Response:</string>
    <string name="drawer_pmgky">PMGKY</string>
    <string name="drawer_evarification">E-Verification of Cash Deposits</string>
    <string name="drawer_activities">Clean Money Activities</string>
    <string name="drawer_participants">Participants</string>
    <string name="drawer_resources">Resources</string>
    <string name="drawer_quickfacts">Quick Facts</string>
    <string name="drawer_socialmediacorner">Social Media Corner</string>
    <string name="drawer_newsupdates">News and Updates</string>
    <string name="drawer_helpdesk">Helpdesk</string>
    <string name="drawer_loginitduser">Login-ITD User</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="drawer_login">Login</string>
    <string name="drawer_operationcleanmoney">Operation Clean Money</string>
    <string name="drawer_mytask">My Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_newtask">New Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_pendingtask">Pending Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_comptask">Completed Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_closedtask">Closed Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_readyforupdate">Ready For Update</string>

    <string name="drawer_closed">Closed</string>
    <string name="drawer_myassigtask">My Assigned Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_createtask">Create Task</string>
    <string name="drawer_training">Training</string>
    <string name="drawer_aboutus">About Us</string>
    <string name="drawer_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="drawer_termscondition">Term &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="drawer_contactus">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="drawer_myaccounts">My Accounts</string>
    <string name="drawer_news">News</string>
    <string name="taskdesc">Description:</string>
    <string name="fav_task">FAVOURITE CONTACTS</string>
    <string name="title">Title*</string>
    <string name="heading">Heading</string>
    <string name="desc">Description*</string>
    <string name="chooseimage">Choose Image</string>
    <string name="url">Url</string>
    <string name="submitt">Submit</string>
    <string name="author">Author</string>
    <string name="drawer_favtask">Favourite</string>
    <string name="drawer_directory">Directory</string>
    <string name="drawer_success_stories">Success Stories</string>
    <string name="drawer_outreach_stories">Outreach</string>

    <string name="drawer_add_stories">Add Stories</string>
    <string name="drawer_edit_stories">Edit Stories</string>
    <string name="drawer_engage">Engage</string>
    <string name="drawer_isupport">I Support</string>
    <string name="clear_date">Clear Date</string>
    <string name="drawer_help">Help</string>
    <string name="no_favtask">No Favourite Contacts</string>
    <string name="details">DETAILS</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="enterpanno">Enter Your PAN</string>
    <string name="valid_email">Please enter valid email id</string>
    <string name="sccessfullogin">Successfully login</string>
    <string name="valid_email_password">Please enter valid email and password</string>
    <string name="choosefile">Please choose a file</string>
    <string name="choosedate">Please choose date</string>
    <string name="select_date">Select date*</string>
    <string name="reassign_content">Task has been Re-Assigned \nPlease refer your mail for more details</string>

    <string name="password_notmatch">Your password and confirmation password do not match.</string>
    <string name="fill_password">Please fill password</string>
    <string name="valid_emailotp">Please enter valid email and OTP</string>
    <string name="went_wrong">Something went wrong please resend OTP</string>
    <string name="enterotp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="confirmation_dialog">Confirmation Dialog</string>
    <string name="otp_send_validation">If you do not receive OTP with in 5 minutes, you may request for another OTP by clicking on the resend OTP Button</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_make_call">Do you want to make call?</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="add_to_fav">Add to Favourite</string>
    <string name="participatess">PARTICIPANTS</string>
    <string name="engage">Engage</string>
    <string name="strpeerknow">LET YOUR PEER KNOW</string>
    <string name="strcontributed">  HAVE YOU CONTRIBUTED ?</string>
    <string name="isupportheader">I Support</string>
    <string name="head1">I promise that</string>
    <string name="head2">I’ll file my return of Income on time</string>
    <string name="head3">I’ll show correct income in my return of income</string>
    <string name="head4">I’ll pay all due taxes on time</string>
    <string name="upload_images">You can upload max 5 images</string>
    <string name="officer_name">Officer Name*</string>
    <string name="designation">Designation*</string>
    <string name="date_of_meetting">Date Of Meeting*</string>
    <string name="venue">Venue Detail*</string>
    <string name="target_audience">Target Audience</string>
    <string name="i_support">TAKE A PLEDGE</string>
    <string name="engaged_join">Have Already\nEngaged with\nOperation Clean Money</string>
    <string name="support_join">Have Already\nSupported\nOperation Clean Money</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Static text for clean money removable -->
    <string name="feedback_content">Thank you for visiting Operation Clean Money and becoming a stackholder in the </string>
    <string name="governance">governance</string>


    <string name="newscontent_details">The government has warned banks of “de-authorisation” of branches if they
        refuse to accept taxes under the amnesty scheme PMGKY, which ends on March 31. The Finance Ministry,
        in a communication to heads of banks which are authorised to accept deposits under the Pradhan Mantri
        Garib Kalyan Yojana (PMGKY), asked them to issue directions to all branches for making necessary changes
        in their system/software to accept the tax.</string>
    <string name="newscontent_details_bottom">“Non-compliance of this order may be viewed seriously and may lead to
        de-authorisation of that branch in case of refusalto accept taxes,” the ministry said.</string>
    <string name="newscontent_details_bottom2">Post demonetisation, the government came out with PMGKY under which people holding unaccounted
        cash can deposit them in bank accounts till March 31 by paying 50 per cent tax plus penalty.
        A quarter of the total sum will have to be parked in a non-interest bearing deposit for four years.
        The scheme opened on December 1.
    </string>
    <string name="newsdetails_header">Government warns banks over non-acceptance of PMGKY tax</string>

    <string name="about_us">Operation Clean Money was launched on 31st January, 2017 by the Income Tax department for
        e-verification of large deposits made between the period of 9th November and 30th December, 2016.</string>
    <string name="about_us1"> Income tax department sent E-mail and SMS to approximately 18 lakh taxpayers who made
        suspicious deposits over Rs 5 lakh during the 50-day demonetisation period, as part of the initiative. The
        operation is primarily aimed to verify cash transaction status (exchange/savings of banned notes) of tax payers
        during the demonetisation period.</string>
    <string name="about_us2">More than 7 Lakh people logged online and acknowledged to have made such deposits. The biggest challenge
        the Income Tax Department is facing is that a large number of people are not registered on the income tax portal.</string>
    <string name="about_us3">Data analytics will be used to select cases for verification, based on approved risk criteria. If the case is
        selected for verification, request for additional information and its response will also be communicated
        electronically. The information on the online portal will be dynamic getting updated on receipt of new
         information, response and data analytics. The response of taxpayer will be assessed against available
        information. In case explanation of source of cash is found justified, the verification will be closed
        without any need to visit Income Tax Office.</string>
    <string name="about_us4"> The verification will also be closed if the cash deposit is declared under Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna(PMGKY).
        It is an amnesty scheme for the defaulters to turn black money into white by declaring their unaccounted money.
        The last date to declare unaccounted money is set as 31st March. However, black money can only be converted to
        white after paying tax, surcharge, and penalty of up to 49.90percent of the total amount. Plus, the 25 percent of the money
        left after the deductions will be locked up in the bank interest-free for the next 4 years.</string>
    <string name="about_us5">Non-disclosure of the undisclosed income before 31st March, 2017 will attract tax, surcharge, and penalty
        amounting to 77.25 percent along with prosecution.</string>
    <string name="about_us6">The money collected under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna will be used to contribute to the cause of
        underprivileged of the country. The decision to give another opportunity to declare undisclosed income is observed as an important
        step to bridge the gap between the rich and the poor of the country.</string>

    <string name="contact_us1">CEO MyGov/Web information Manager</string>
    <string name="contact_us2">MyGov Cell</string>
    <string name="contact_us4">3rd Floor, Room no-3015</string>
    <string name="contact_us5">Ministry of Electronics and Information Technology</string>
    <string name="contact_us6">Load Road New Delhi - 110003</string>
    <string name="contact_us7">India</string>


    <string name="help1">This section attempts to help you easily navigate through the pages of this portal. We strive
    to provide you a pleasant experience while browsing the portal.Sections of this portal Sections of this website are
    Dashboard, Blog, Talk, Feedback, FAQ, About Us, Contact Us, Sitemap, Terms &amp; Conditions.</string>
    <string name="helpheading1">Viewing information in various file formats</string>

    <string name="help2">To view the information properly, your browser need to have the required plug-ins. All the
    information provided by this website is available in PDF, and HTML format. In case, your browser doesn’t have the
    required plug-ins or softwares, you can download it for free from the internet.</string>
    <string name="helpheading2">Accessibility Help</string>

    <string name="help3">The accessibility option provided by this website allows you to increase the text size and
    changing the contrast scheme for clear visibility and better readability.</string>
    <string name="helpheading3">Changing the Text Size</string>
    <string name="help4">You can change the text to smaller or bigger from its standard size on this portal. You can choose any one of the three options provided:
                        Small : It displays information in the smallest font size available on the portal.
                        Medium : It is the standard default font size of the portal.
                        Large : It displays information in the smallest font size available on the portal.</string>


    <!-- terms and conditions-->

    <string name="termscondition1">These terms of use describe your rights and responsibilities as a user of the
        mygov.in (MyGov).To have a MyGov account, you must accept these terms of use. MyGov, NIC, DeitY and Govt. of India reserve the right to
        make changes to MyGov and these terms of use at any time. If those changes affect your rights or responsibilities, you
        will be notified through MyGov.</string>
    <string name="termscondition2">The following terms of use supersede and replace any terms and conditions you may have previously
        accepted governing your use of MyGov. The following Terms &amp; Conditions come into effect as soon as you have accepted it
        and created your MyGov account.</string>
    <string name="termscondition3">As a user of MyGov you are granted a nonexclusive, nontransferable, revocable, limited license to
        access and use MyGov and content in accordance with these Terms of Use. Provider may terminate this license at any time for any reason.
        MyGov designed &amp; hosted by National Informatics Centre, Contents provided by the various Organizations, Departments and Ministries of
        Government of India.Though all efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy and currency of the content on MyGov, the same should not
        be construed as a statement of law or used for any legal purposes. In case of any ambiguity or doubts, users are advised to verify/check
        with the concerned Ministry/Department/Organization and/or other source(s), and to obtain appropriate professional advice.
        Under no circumstances will the Government Ministry/Department/Organization be liable for any expense, loss or damage including, without
        limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any expense, loss or damage whatsoever arising from use, or loss of use, of data,
        arising out of or in connection with the use of MyGov.</string>
    <string name="termsconditionheading1">LIMITATION ON USE:</string>
    <string name="termscondition4">The Content on MyGov is for your personal use only and not for commercial exploitation. You may not decompile,
        reverse engineer, disassemble, rent, lease, loan, sell, sublicense, or create derivative works from MyGov. Nor may you use any network
        monitoring or discovery software to determine the site architecture, or extract information about usage, individual identities or users.
        You will not use any robot, spider, other automatic software or device, or manual process to monitor or copy MyGov without Provider’s
        prior written permission. You will not copy, modify, reproduce, republish, distribute, display, or transmit for commercial, non-profit
        or public purposes all or any portion of MyGov, except to the extent permitted by the copyright policy of this terms of use.
        Any unauthorized use of MyGov is prohibited. The use of any software (e.g. bots, scraper tools) or other automatic devices to access,
        monitor or copy the website pages is prohibited unless expressly authorized by the MyGov in writing.</string>
    <string name="termsconditionheading2">POLICY WITH REGARD TO YOUR CONTENT:</string>

    <string name="termscondition5">Uploading content or submitting any materials for use on MyGov, you grant (or warrant that the owner of such
        rights has expressly granted) MyGov a perpetual, worldwide, royalty-free, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license, with right to
        sublicense, to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, publicly perform, publicly display, digitally display and digitally perform
        translate, create derivative works from and distribute such materials or incorporate such materials into any form, medium, or technology
        now known or later developed throughout the universe. You agree that you shall have no recourse against Provider for any alleged or actual
        infringement or misappropriation of any proprietary right in your communications to us.</string>


    <!--PMGKY-->
    <string name="aboutpmgky1">Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna, 2016 (PMGKY) is an amnesty scheme launched in December 2016 by the Government of India.
        This scheme provides one more opportunity to declare unaccounted money till 31st March 2017. The Pradhan Mantri Kalyan Yojna can only be availed
        to declare income in the form of cash or bank deposits in Indian Bank accounts and not in the form of assets/stocks/overseas accounts.</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgky2" translatable="false">Anyone who declares his/her undisclosed income by 31st March 2017 under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna, will have to
        pay tax, surcharge, and penalty of up to 49.90% of the total amount. The 25% of the rest money left after the deductions will be locked up in the
        bank interest-free for the next 4 years. Non-disclosure of the undisclosed income will attract tax, surcharge, and penalty amounting to 77.25% along
        with prosecution.</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgky3">The identity of the person declaring undisclosed income under the Pradhan Mantri Garin Kalyan Yojna will be kept confidential
        and the income declared translatable="false" under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna shall not be taxable under the income-tax Act, 1961.</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgky4">The money collected under the Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojna will be used to contribute to the cause of underprivileged of
        the country. The decision to give another opportunity to declare undisclosed income is observed as an important step to bridge the gap between the
        rich and the poor of the country.</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyheading1">Forms &amp; Acknowledgement</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyheading2">FAQ</string>


    <!-- FAQs pmgky questions and answers-->
    <string name="aboutpmgkyqus1">What is Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Deposit Scheme (PMGKDS), 2016 ?</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyans1">Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Deposit Scheme (PMGKDS), 2016 is a scheme notified by the Government of India on December 16, 2016 which is applicable
        to every declarant under the Taxation and Investment Regime for Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojana, 2016.</string>

    <string name="aboutpmgkyqus2">Who is eligible to deposit in PMGKS?</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyans2">The deposit under this Scheme shall be made by any person who declares undisclosed income under sub-section (1) of section 199C of the Taxation and
        Investment Regime for Pradhan Mantri Garib Kalyan Yojana, 2016.</string>

    <string name="aboutpmgkyqus3">In what form will the deposits under this scheme be held?</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyans3">The Deposits shall be held at the credit of the declarant in Bond Ledger Accounts (BLA) maintained with Reserve Bank of India.</string>

    <string name="aboutpmgkyqus4">Which are the authorized agencies where the application and amount of deposit will be accepted?</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyans4">Application and amount for the deposit (in the form of Bond Ledger Account) shall be received by any banking company, other than Co-operative Banks,
        to which the Banking Regulation Act, 1949 (10 of 1949) applies (Authorised Banks).</string>

    <string name="aboutpmgkyqus5">Where can declarants get the application form?</string>
    <string name="aboutpmgkyans5">Application for the deposit will be available at branches
        of Authorised Banks. It is also available in the Reserve Bank of India website.</string>


    <string name="nationallevel">PAN Allotment - Taxpayer Status(2016-17)</string>
    <string name="statelevelheading">Tax Revenues (INR Billions): 2016-2017</string>
    <string name="stateleveldetail">This is a list of States of India by projected own tax revenues of their governments (excluding the shares from Union tax pool) assessed for
        the year 2010–15 by the Thirteenth Finance Commission with figures in crore of Indian Rupees. Data for Union territories are not available.</string>
    <string name="feedback">Thank You for visiting Operation Clean Money and becoming a stakeholder in the governance procedure of the country. We would like
        to get your valuable feedback on how we can make the governance process better.</string>
    <string name="drawer_faqs">FAQs</string>

    <string name="task_no">Task No:</string>
    <string name="respondedby">Responded By:</string>
    <string name="assigned_on">Assigned On:</string>
    <string name="assigned_by">Assigned By:</string>
    <string name="respondedon">Responded On:</string>
    <string name="assigned_to">Assigned To:</string>
    <string name="task_completion">Task Completion On:</string>
    <string name="subject">Subject:</string>
    <string name="task_completion_date">Task Completion Date:</string>
    <string name="task_completion_on">Task Completion On:</string>
    <string name="assign_task">ASSIGNED NEW TASK DEATILS</string>
    <string name="dashboard">DASHBOARD</string>
    <string name="inprogress_task">IN PROGRESS TASKS</string>
    <string name="no_outreachlist">No Outreach Activities</string>
    <string name="out_reach">OUTREACH ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="closed_task">CLOSED TASKS</string>
    <string name="message">Message:</string>
    <string name="completed_task">COMPLETED TASK:</string>
    <string name="status">Status:</string>
    <string name="todo_task">TO DO TASK</string>
    <string name="mis_name">Name</string>
    <string name="mis_value">Value</string>
    <string name="new_taskk">New</string>
    <string name="new_assignmnt">New Assignment</string>
    <string name="wip"></string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="pending_task">PENDING TASKS</string>
    <string name="pending_taskk">Pending</string>
    <string name="in_progress">In Progress</string>

    <string name="ready_for_update">Ready for update</string>
    <string name="for_review">For Review</string>

    <string name="titlee">Title:</string>
    <string name="authorr">Author:</string>
    <string name="created_on">Created On:</string>
    <string name="click_view"><u>Read More</u></string>
    <string name="success_storiess">SUCCESS STORIES</string>
    <string name="success_story">SUCCESS STORY</string>

    <string-array name="array_name">
        <item>Select MIS Type</item>
        <item>E-Verification</item>
        <!--<item>Array Item Two</item>
        <item>Array Item Three</item>-->
    </string-array>


    <string name="resToastText"></string>
    <string name="isupport">I SUPPORT OPERATION CLEAN MONEY</string>
    <string name="close_task">Closed</string>
    <string name="task_monitoring">TASK MONITORING</string>
    <string name="no_task">No New Task</string>
    <string name="no_pendingtask">No Pending Task</string>
    <string name="no_desiganationtask">No Record Found</string>
    <string name="no_completedtask">No Completed Task </string>
    <string name="no_closedtask">No Closed Task</string>
    <string name="choosedocpdf">file type must be pdf or doc</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit Successfully</string>
    <string name="filter_mis">MIS Filters</string>
    <string name="filter_mis_type">MIS Type</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="confirmpasswrd">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="selectmembers">Select Members</string>
    <string name="selectsearch">Select Search Option</string>
    <string name="tagyourself">TAG YOURSELF</string>
    <string name="drawer_add_outreach">Add Outreach</string>
    <string name="drawer_edit_outreach">Edit Outreach</string>
    <string name="wentwrongmsg">Something went wrong...</string>
    <string name="favourite">Favourite</string>
    <string name="create_task">Create Task</string>
    <string name="task_dashboard">TASK DASHBOARD</string>
    <string name="new_user">NEW USER? GET PASSWORD</string>
    <string name="create_task_detail">CREATE TASK DETAILS</string>
    <string name="user_name">Name</string>
    <string name="user_email">Email</string>
    <string name="user_call">Call</string>
    <string name="user_designation">Designation</string>
    <string name="user_level">Level</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="task">Task</string>
    <string name="closed">Closed</string>
    <string name="directory_dash">DIRECTORY</string>
    <string name="create_task_dash">CREATE TASK</string>
    <string name="favourite_dash">FAVOURITE</string>
    <string name="to_do_task">TO DO TASK</string>
    <string name="task_monitoring_dash">TASK MONITORING</string>
    <string name="out_reach_dash">OUTREACH ACTIVITIES</string>
    <string name="success_stories_dash">SUCCESS STORIES</string>
    <string name="un_fav">Un Favourite</string>
    <string name="searchby_name">SEARCH BY NAME</string>
    <string name="searchby_designation">SEARCH BY DESIGNATION</string>
    <string name="under_development">Functionality under development...</string>
    <string name="enteritdname">Enter Name of ITD Official</string>
    <string name="assign_task_to_user">ASSIGN TASK</string>
    <string name="no_success_stories">No Success Stories</string>
    <string name="out_reach_activity">OUTREACH ACTIVITY</string>
    <string name="task_completed_on">Task Completed On</string>
    <string name="closed_task_details">CLOSED TASK DETAILS</string>
    <string name="inprogress_details">IN PROGRESS TASK DETAILS</string>
    <string name="task_for_review">TASKS FOR REVIEW</string>
    <string name="for_reaview_task_details">FOR REVIEW TASK DETAILS</string>
    <string name="drawer_search_byname">Search By Name</string>
    <string name="drawer_designation">Search By Designation</string>
    <string name="drawer_cleanmoneyparticipants">Clean Money Participants</string>
    <string name="subdrawer_engage">Engage</string>
    <string name="subdrawer_isupport">I Support</string>
    <string name="subdrawer_contribute">Contribute</string>
    <string name="task_deskboard">Task Dashboard</string>
    <string name="drawer_outreach_activities">Outreach Activities</string>
    <string name="no_assigendtask">No Assigned New Task</string>
    <string name="no_taskinprogress">No Task In Progress</string>
    <string name="n_taskforreview">No Task For Review</string>
    <string name="no_assignedclose">No Assigned Closed Task</string>
    <string name="searchby_deasignation">SEARCH BY DESIGNATION</string>
    <string name="no_of_participnts">No Of Participents*</string>
    <string name="pincode">Pincode*</string>
    <string name="activities">Activity Details*</string>
    <string name="topic">Topic*</string>
    <string name="create_by">Created By:</string>
    <string name="prvious_attach">Previous Attachment</string>
    <string name="current_attach">Current Attachment</string>
    <string name="response_chain">Response</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="local_message">Local Message:</string>
    <string name="_2_sufficient_internet_bandwidth">2. Sufficient internet bandwidth.</string>
    <string name="please_check">Please check:</string>
    <string name="oops">Oops!!</string>
    <string name="_1_you_are_connected_to_internet">1. You are connected to internet.</string>
    <string name="error_message">message block can not be blank.</string>
    <string name="engage_joinus">Join us to stay updated about all actions, events and activities happening at Operation Clean Money</string>
    <string name="view_attachment">Click here to view</string>

    <string name="title_please_state">Please Select Your State</string>
    <string name="title_please_area">Please enter your area code</string>
    <string name="title_please_contribution">Please a type of contribution</string>

    <string name="title_details">have Already to Contributed\nto Operation clean Money</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">729439290567709</string>

</resources>

